<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://docs.fnfcentral.com/blog</id>
    <title>FNF Central Docs Blog</title>
    <updated>2021-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://docs.fnfcentral.com/blog"/>
    <subtitle>FNF Central Docs Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://docs.fnfcentral.com/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[0.0.5 Release and First Outage]]></title>
        <id>0.0.5-and-outages</id>
        <link href="https://docs.fnfcentral.com/blog/0.0.5-and-outages"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[0.0.5]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>0.0.5</h2><p>This is mostly a QoL update, with a few new nice features. Nothing groundbreaking, as I am currently on Holiday vacation in a totally different state.</p><h2>The Outage</h2><p>At approximately 23:50 UTC on the 23rd, one of the worker nodes went offline. Within 5 minuets the entire cluster had collapsed, as there are only two worker nodes in the Canary. The server was back online 00:19 on the 24th.</p><p><img src="./DoBetter.gif" alt="Boyfriend Miss"/></p><p>Thanks to some late notice from Linode, I learned that this was a hardware failure that forced them to relocate my node which was running one of the two workers, bringing it offline for about 30 minuets. Why it took that long, don&#x27;t ask me. All this really proved was that the official cluster will be at least three nodes.</p><h2>Changes in The Update</h2><h3>New Features</h3><ul><li>Account Recovery (Yes I Know Email Still Does Not Work On the Canary)</li><li>Added Error Page</li><li>Added Dashboard (Kinda)</li></ul><h3>Changes</h3><ul><li>Added Output for Registration and Login</li><li>Removed FNF OG From Home Page As It Longer Is Supported</li></ul><h3>Bug Fixes</h3><ul><li>Fixed Weird Bug That Rarely Happens On Game Page</li></ul>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph (JRed)</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/jredow</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canary Initial Deployment]]></title>
        <id>canary-deployment</id>
        <link href="https://docs.fnfcentral.com/blog/canary-deployment"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Canary?]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Canary?</h2><p>To test everything, we deploy a small test site just like the main server to make sure everything goes okay. Upon launch, it will be brought down, but it will come back occasionally for testing and community feedback purposes.</p><h2>Canary Deployment Retrospective</h2><p>Well the deployment... went well, but anything but smooth. We are now on version 0.0.4, all in one day.</p><p><img src="./DoBetter.gif" alt="Boyfriend Miss"/></p><p>It could have gone worse of course. After 0.0.3 it was pretty stable, just 0.0.4 was needed as it added a ton of security fixes with the Helm chart. Expect actual posts on every version from this point on!</p><p>See you all later, and have a great Holiday!</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph (JRed)</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/jredow</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome To The FNF Docs!]]></title>
        <id>welcome-to-docs</id>
        <link href="https://docs.fnfcentral.com/blog/welcome-to-docs"/>
        <updated>2021-11-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi 🙂]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2>Hi 🙂</h2><p>Welcome the the new FNF Central Docs! This site will include documentation on a ton of things (internal and external), such as the SuperSickAPI, the api (private and public), testing and deploying FNF Central, and soon more!</p><p>Expect this site to change a ton in the first few months of FNF Central.</p><p><img src="./Boyfriend.png" alt="Boyfriend"/></p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Joseph (JRed)</name>
            <uri>https://github.com/jredow</uri>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>